Kthan Graham

3300 Glayds, Largo 33774 ♦ 813-727-0464 ♦ Website KthanGraham@hotmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

With a background in object and non-object programming, Connectwise Service Delivery experience, and Project Management, I understand the importance of understanding the partner side of the product. Building on my experiences, I hope to contribute by utilizing my knowledge of Javascriplt, C#, SQL, and C. I look forward to expanding my knowledge and experience with real world applications.

EDUCATION

University of South Florida, Tampa

Bachelor of Health Science, concentration in HR management 3.0 GPA

Tampa, FL Graduated 2018

Hillsborough Community College, Brandon

Associates of science, Associates in Programing 3.0 GPA

Tampa, FL 2019-Current

<u>Relevant Coursework:</u> Programming Logic, Database Design, Computer Operating Systems, Intro to Networking, Java Programming, Advanced Java 2, Programming in C#, Mgmt Info Sys., Programming in C, and received a Programing Specialist Certificate.

<u>Relevant Projects (Website)</u>: Payroll Calculator, Grade calculator, Multiples finder, Hurricane scale announcer, lowest cash denominator, Payroll register, GPA reader, Tax calculator, Number game, Net earnings, Payroll sheet, Word counter, Discord API word assassin game, and a file directory search engine.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Connectwise March 2021 - Current

Ir. Business Knowledge Expert

Largo, FL

- Server level technical skills: server builds and administration, setup and support, virtual environment administration.
- Analyze, test, and modify partner and end user customer's computer systems based upon their unique design specifications and/or computing environment.
- Interact with partners and end users to provide support via phone, ticket system and chat and answer user inquiries regarding their systems with the ability to fully explain what the issue is and how to solve it.
- One of the top performers for 3 months in a row (top 5).

Oasis Paychex April 2019 – October 2019

PEO Specialist/HR consultant

Tampa, FL

- Prototyped the new payroll/HR backend.
- Developed Excel charts to help provide better QA on payrolls.
- Handled 50+ Clients Payrolls and assisted in their Human resources.
- Collaborated with senior leadership to determine the best course of action and develop new training programs to increase retainment in the company.
- Generated and uploaded weekly Payroll and HR reports for all clients.
- Left to pursue education in programming.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Training: Completion of 91 education courses through Paychex, 4 years of communication technology courses, 89+ college credits, and a Programming Specialist Certificate.

- Leadership/Organizations: Company commander JROTC, Team lead in documentary competition, ISVM at Tillys.
- Skills: SQL data management, IT problem solving, HTML background, work with HR databases, Payroll, Pseudo code syntax, Modular Programming.
- Activities: Balloon comity at Paychex, Building multiple apps, Film competitions, 3D printing, 360Food.